Who do you see when you look at Liverpool?
Can you see the one?
Do you see the thousands of people
who don't know Jesus?
We're surrounded by people
from across the world.
How many know Jesus and who he really is?
How many have the opportunity to
experience a community of Christians
living out faith in him?
We believe that God has given us a vision
for a vibrant city centre church
that is for Liverpool
and is loving the whole world.
And we have a dream for a building of
our own in the heart of the city.
We've been on this journey
now for 20 years.
Since we began in 2003, the idea behind
the church has remained the same:
most people have not rejected the gospel,
they've just not heard and experienced it.
Here in the UK our church grouping, the
FIEC, have done research that suggests
less than 3% of people have any meaningful
connection with any church at all.
And Liverpool is a place just like that.
Many people disconnected from church,
but not against it.
They've just not experienced it.
So we thought, you can have a church where
people really understand the Bible
for themselves,
where people can ask any question and
receive a good answer, where people can
experience the best things there are to
experience of our Christian community.
And a church where people, if they want to
be, can be invested in and trained and
sent out into the world.
Within a year of our church starting we'd
outgrown our venue, which held a hundred
people, and since then we've continued to
grow — not only our church, but starting or
revitalising six new churches in
Liverpool and the North West region.
And the story goes on.
Lives are being changed, churches are
being revitalised, God is at work.
We praise God for his amazing grace
towards us, and for all he's done
through us over the years,
and all he's doing now.
God is using us in our Sunday services and
ministries, through the sharing of our
lives as we meet together
in small groups across the city,
and through the sharing of our faith.
It is such a joy to see so many people of
different ages, backgrounds and
nationalities being baptised, being
discipled and growing in their faith.
We long to see this more and more.
We want to invite the thousands of people
in Liverpool to come and experience our
church community,
to come and meet Jesus Christ.
We want to continue to grow, but for a
number of years we've been limited by not
having our own building.
We're not able to welcome more people,
and we long for more freedom
with the space we have.
Being tenants and not owners
is highly restrictive,
it's inefficient and it's insecure.
We've struggled with our location.
We really want to be a much more
accessible and visible presence in the city.
Having our Sunday services and midweek
events in different venues can be unclear
and unhelpful.
It is our dream to have a home of our own
in the heart of the city.
Imagine a place where we can do everything
under one roof, a place which is
multifunctional, spacious and welcoming.
Imagine the freedom we would have as we
run our church services, events,
ministries — and even do more.
Imagine a building or a site
that lets us grow, so we can reach
the thousands of people, disciple, train
and send them back into our great city.
This is our dream.
Imagine a place like this, a place that's
a visible, accessible home to welcome
people in.
Not for comfort,
but to be gathered and sent out.
A secure hub in which we can disciple,
train and send out the future leaders.
A solid foundation to plant and revitalise
many churches for decades to come.
We believe that this is the church that
Liverpool, the wider region and the UK
desperately needs.
But we're not there yet.
We still face many challenges.
But we believe God has led us to this
point, and we confidently trust in him for
every step that remains.
We need your help.
Will you consider partnering with us by
faithfully praying, widely sharing, and
generously giving?
Your generosity will help us secure this
building and turn it into a home that
truly serves Liverpool and beyond.
Our city has hundreds of thousands who are
hungry for community, for
belonging,
for meaning.
Many are searching and open to Jesus.
We believe that God will use this home to
reach them, grow his church and
bring glory to his name.
And we'd love for you to be
a part of this exciting project.